Guide to the Pauline Park Papers TAM.663
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Pauline Park Papers
1986-2015, undated
2000-2015
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Park, Pauline
TAM.663
7.25 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing.
3 videocassettes (vhs)
10 audiocassettes
951 Megabytes in 92 computer files.
The Pauline Park Papers contains material from 1986-2015 documenting the advocacy, activism, and writing of Pauline Park, a transgender activist, speaker, writer, and educator. A large portion of the collection contains material from the New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy (NYAGRA) and Queens Pride House (QPH) two organizations that Park helped co-found, in 1998 and 1997, respectively, and lead. Park campaigned for the transgender rights law enacted by the New York City Council in 2002, and in 2005 became the first openly transgender grand marshal of the New York City Pride March. Park has been the keynote speaker at many LGBT and Asian American conferences and events held in the United States. She has written extensively about arts and culture, music, spirituality, politics, theatre, race, and LGBT health and rights. Her writing has been published in journals, newspapers, and newsletters. This collection contains materials on subjects such as transgender health, identity, community, and public policy, and includes correspondence, board meeting minutes, photographs, VHS tapes, conference name badges, certificates, audio recordings, original poetry and creative writing, notes, speeches, flyers and programs for events and conferences related to QPH and NYAGRA, press featuring Park, and letters to politicians and allied organizations advocating the passage of LGTBQ inclusion and non-discrimination legislation.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
Donated by Pauline Park in 2015. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2015.004, 2015.055, and 2015.059.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into four series. The collection is arranged into groupings by subject matter that reflect the original order in which the collection was donated to the Tamiment Library. The arrangement is as follows:
I. Organizations, 1986-2015, undated
II. Writings, Publications, and Other Related Creative Projects, 1989-2015, undated
III. Events, 1990-2014, undated
IV. Personal, 1994-2015, undated
Historical/Biographical Note
Pauline Park (1960- ) is a transgender activist based in New York City who received her PhD in Political Science from the University of Illinois. Park was born in Korea, and was adoped and raised by European American parents. As of 2019, she is the President of the Board of Directors and Acting Executive Director of Queens Pride House (QPH) and Chair of the New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy (NYAGRA). Park led the campaign for the transgender rights law enacted by the New York City Council in 2002, and in 2005 became the first openly transgender grand marshal of the New York City Pride March. Pauline has written widely on LGBTQ issues and has conducted transgender sensitivity training sessions for a wide range of organizations. She was the subject of the 2008 documentary Envisioning Justice: The Journey of a Transgendered Woman. Park was named to Huffington Post's list of "The Most Influential LGBT Asian Icons" and to a list of "50 Transgender Icons" on the Transgender Day of Remembrance in 2012.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains materials related to the advocacy, activism, and writing of Pauline Park from 1986 to 2015. The bulk of the material in this collection comes from the early 1990s to the mid 2010s, and documents Park's work as co-founder and co-leader of the New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy, the first New York statewide transgender advocacy organization, and Queens Pride House, the LGBT community center of Queens, New York. The collection contains some of Park's published and unpublished writing which addresses topics of transgender health, identity, community, and public policy as well as race, national identity, philosophy, spirituality, and the arts. Materials in the collection include correspondence, programs, digital images, photographs, VHS and audio cassette tapes, conference name badges, certificates, audio recordings, original poetry and creative writing, flyers for events and conferences related to Queens Pride House (QPH) and the New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy (NYAGRA) and other organizations. There are a number of press clippings and magazine articles featuring Park as well as letters to politicians, and allied organizations advocating the passage of LGTBQ non-discrimination legislation. The collection also contains a number of documentaries about or featuring Park and a sound recording of Park preforming classical piano music. Park donated the proceeds of the sound recording to NYAGRA and QPH.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Custodial History
These materials were solicited by Laura Chen Schulz Deputy Director of New York University's Asian/Pacific/American Institute and Tim Naftali, Tamiment Director and shipped direct to Tamiment by Pauline Park. Initially, five boxes were donated to Tamiment on January 25, 2015 which comprised the 2015.004 accession. The rest of the boxes were received from Pauline Park on unknown dates in 2015.
Electronic Records Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Political activists -- United States.; Transgender people -- United States; Gender discrimination.; Gay and lesbian film festivals. -- 21st century; LGBTQ+ activism; Transgender people -- Civil rights.; Asian Americans -- Political activity; Asian American LGBTQ+ people; Gender identity -- United States; Gender, sexuality & culture; Transgender activism; New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy; Park, Pauline
- Series I. Organizations, 1986-2015, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes.; 106 kilobytes in 1 computer file.; 5 audiocassettes
  Arrangement
  This series is grouped by organization, then arranged alphabetically by title.
  Scope and Contents
  Material in this series largely contains material from Pauline Park's work with the New York Association for Gender Rights Advocacy (NYAGRA) and Queens Pride House from the 1900s to the mid 2010s. Most the materials in this series documents Park's work applying to various grants, speaking at various events,and writing letters regarding New York State's Dignity for All Students Act on behalf of NYAGRA. There are some material from other LGBT and Asian American organizations as well. Material in this series includes: board meeting minutes, audio recordings, notes, correspondence between Park and NYAGRA/QPH members, certificates of incorporation, grant proposals and reports, flyers, press, testimony, information packets, and brochures.
  There is some born-digital media--one Word document--in this series.
  - Amnesty International Material on Police Misconduct and Abuse, 2004; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Christine Quinn: The Anybody but Quinn Campaign, 2003-2013; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cielo Latino, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The Dari Project, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dumbarton United Methodist Church, 2003; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Gay Asian and Pacific Islander Men of New York, 1998-2004, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gay Asian and Pacific Islander Men of New York: Posters (Gay is Good!), undated; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Queens, 2002-2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Queens: Candidates, 2001-2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Queens: Membership Forms and Newsletters, 2002-2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Queens: Newsletters and Organizational Materials, 1986-2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Queens: Press, 2001-2009; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Guillmero Vasquez Independent Democratic Club of Quees, the Audre Lorde Project, and the Sylvia Rivera Law Project, 2002-2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Community Center: 2004-2005 Annual Report, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Directory of Services and Resources New York Metropolitan Area, 2000-2003; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center: Press, 1998; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - NYAGRA: Anniversary, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NYAGRA: Articles, 1993-2011; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - NYAGRA: Articles of Incorporation, 2000-2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYAGRA: Ben and Jerry's Foundation Grant Proposal, 2002-2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYAGRA: Brochures and Correspondence, 2004-2011, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - NYAGRA: Budget 2000-2002, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYAGRA: Business Cards for Pauline Park, undated; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYAGRA: Correspondence, 2000-2013, undated; 3 folders (Box 6, Folder 1, Box 16, Folder 13, Box 17)
  - NYAGRA: Correspondence -- Brown, Marlene Rebecca, 2004; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - NYAGRA: Correspondence -- Dignity for All Students Act, 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NYAGRA: Development Plan 2005-2006, undated; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 18, 25)
  - NYAGRA: Discrimination Survey, 1998-2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NYAGRA: Draft Guidelines Regarding "Gender Identity" Discrimination in New York City, 2001-2004; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYAGRA: Events, 2001-2013, undated; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NYAGRA: Finances, 2010-2011; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NYAGRA: Financial Records 2006, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NYAGRA: Financial Records 2007, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NYAGRA: Financial Report 2007, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NYAGRA: Fiscal Sponsorship, 2002; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NYAGRA: Flyer and Correspondence, 2004; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - NYAGRA: Funding, 2005, undated; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYAGRA: Grant from the New York City Department of Youth and Community Development, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 21, 22)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposals, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Fund for Creative Communities/Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 2004; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to the Gill Foundation, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Mertz Gilmore Foundation, 2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to New York Foundation, 2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Open Society Institute, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to OUT Fund, 2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Resist Foundation, 2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Stonewall Community Foundation, 2000-2004; 3 folders (Box 5, Folder 10-12)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Proposal to Tides Foundation, 2003; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Report to New York Community Trust, 2005; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 6, Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Report to North Star Fund, 2002-2005; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NYAGRA: Grant Research, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 19, Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NYAGRA: Internet Resources, 2002; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NYAGRA: Job Search for Grant Writers, Designers, and Others, 2002-2005, undated; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NYAGRA: Legislation, Regulations, and Public Policy, 2000-2014; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYAGRA: Letters to New York City Council Re: Dignity in All Schools Act, 2004; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - NYAGRA: Mailing List (Blanks) with Article, 2004; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - NYAGRA: Sound Recording "Interview on Out FM (WBAI) -- Park, Pauline and D. Cartwright", undated (Box 8, Cassette 663.008)
  - NYAGRA: Sound Recordings of Meetings, 2002 (Box 8, Cassette 663.001, 663.003, 663.005, 663.009)
  - NYAGRA: Membership List, 2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_TAM_663_ER_2)
  - NYAGRA: National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 2003-2005; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NYAGRA: New York City Department of Youth and Community Development, 2001; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NYAGRA: New York State Charities Bureau Filing, 2003-2007; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYAGRA: Newsletter and Logo, 2002-2004, undated; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYAGRA: Organizational Materials, 2001-2011, undated; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 8, Box 15, Folder 6)
  - NYAGRA: The Paul Rapoport Foundation Inc., 1999-2004; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYAGRA: Press, 2004-2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYAGRA: Revenue from Speaking/Training, 2010-2011; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYAGRA: Staff, 2001-2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYAGRA: Testimony to New York City Department of Health and Hygiene, 2006; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NYAGRA: Transgender Health Care Provider Directory, 2009; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - NYAGRA Crisis: Documents (Conspirators), 2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NYAGRA Crisis: Legal Correspondence, 2000-2002; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NYAGRA in the Press, 1993-2011, undated; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 27, Box 6, Folder 7)
  - NYAGRA and Queens Pride House Materials, 2003, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - NYAGRA Testimonies, Queens Pride House Press and Flyers, Article Drafts, and Notes, 2012-2013, undated; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union and the Policy Institute of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force: Reports, 2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations, 1995-2007; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: Press Releases, 2002-2010; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Out People of Color Political Action Club (Out PocPAC), 2001-2003, undated; 3 folders (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - Out People of Color Political Action Club: Press Coverage, 2001-2004, undated; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Paul Rapoport Foundation Inc, 2005; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Queens Pride House, 1997-2014, undated; 6 folders (Box 3, Folder 1-5, Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Queens Pride House: Anniversary Reception Programs, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Queens Pride House: Board Meetings and Agendas, 2014-2015; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Queens Pride House: Correspondence, 2012-2014; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Queens Pride House: Financials, 2014; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Queens Pride House: Flyers, Programs, Press, and Articles, 2004-2013, undated; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Queens Pride House: Gender Identity Project, 1998-2001; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Queens Pride House: Jesus Baez and Rene Vazquez del Valle Correspondence, 2014-2015; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Queens Pride House: Legal Services, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Queens Pride House: Needs Assessment, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Queens Pride House: Newsletters, 1997-2004; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Queens Pride House: Press, 1997-2012; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Queens Pride House Board of Directors: Minutes of Meetings, 1997-2014; 5 folders (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
  - Queens Pride House/NYAGRA, 2003-2014, undated; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Queers Against Israeli Apartheid, 2011-2012; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Transgender Health Initiative of New York, 2004-2008, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Transgender Legal Defense and Education Fund: Meeting Minutes, 2010; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Transgender Legal Defense and Education Fund: Press, 2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Transgender Legal Defense and Education Fund: Program Evaluation Forms, 2006; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series II. Writings, Publications, and Other Related Creative Projects, 1989-2015, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 4.5 manuscript boxes.; 669 Megabytes in 2 computer files.
  This series is grouped by title, then arranged in alphabetical order.
  This series contains published and unpublished creative, critical, academic, and personal written material by Park from the late 1990s to the mid 2010s. The material in this series includes drafts of personal essays, articles published in LGBT magazines, VHS tapes, published letters to newspaper editors, book chapters, poetry, a play script, and an audio recording of Park playing the piano.
  There are some born-digital media--two audio files--in this series.
  - Academic Article, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Academic Articles, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Article Draft: "Homeward Bound: The Journey of a Transgendered Korean Adoptee", 2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Autobiographical Writings, 2004-2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Briefing Document: "The Transgender Movement in International Perspective", 2005; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Dignity for All Students Act, 2003-2005; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Gender Identity Studies Material, 2000; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Go! Magazine, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Guidelines Regarding Gender Identity Discrimination in New York City (Draft), 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Iban/Queer Koreans of New York Press, 1998-2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Iban/Queer Koreans of New York Publications, 1998-2001, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journal Articles, 1995-2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Legislation Information and Letters of Support, 2002-2005; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Magazines, 2002-2005, undated; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Honorable Stephen M. Saland (Senator), 2004; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "The Man Who Would Be Queen" Review, Gay Today, 7.10.2008, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New Jersey Lewdness Statute Article, 2006; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New York Birth Certificate Regulations for Transgender People (Proposed), 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - New York Civil Rights Law, 2001; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - News Magazines (PersuAsian, Gay Asian and Pacific Islander Men of New York), 1997-2006; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 1, 2)
  - Newspaper Articles and Clippings, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Non-Discrimination Policies (St. Vincent Manhattan), 2004; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Opposite the Editorial Articles, 2001-2007, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings and Articles, 2000-2008; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 2003-2012; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Published Article: "Gender at its Core", 2003; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Published Articles, 1998-2013, undated; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Published Book Chapters, 2004-2009; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Radical Faeries Newsletters: FaerieGrams, 1997-2002; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 3, 4)
  - Script, Press, and Production Information: "Undesirable Elements" Play, 2007-2008; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 10, 11)
  - Sound Recording: Barricades Mysterieuses Piano Music Performed by Pauline Park, 2010 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_TAM_663_ER_3)
  - Stage Play Script: In the Realm of Light and Darkness A Short History of the Rise and Fall of Liu An, King of Huai-Nan, 1989; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Writings, 1997-2015, undated; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 15, Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Writings: Letters to the Editor, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Writings in Publications, 1998-2009; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Series III. Events, 1990-2014, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 4.5 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing.; 282 Megabytes in 89 computer files.; 2 audiocassettes
  Material in this series is grouped by file title, then arranged in chronological order.
  This series contains ephemera from the many events where Park was a speaker, panelist moderator, participant, or attendee. The bulk of the material from this series comes from 1997-2014. Of note in this series are flyers, programs, and press from 2005 when Park was the first openly transgender marshall in the New York City Pride March and name badges from events that Park participated in. There is a sound recording on two audiocassettes of an interview with Lee Chung-Woo (Chingusai-Seoul). Ephemera from this series include: flyers, programs, brochures, speaking contracts, speeches, digital images, photographs, testimony from court cases, correspondence, and legal notices from court cases.
  There are some born-digital media--image files--in this series.
  - Speaking Engagement 1990, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Speaking Engagements 1996, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1997-2011; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 7, 8)
  - The Audre Lorde Project: Center for Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Two Spirit, and Transgender People of Color Communities and Audre Lorde Project's Working Group on Women's Organizing Arms Akimbo Conference, 1998; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Conference Papers, 1998-2011; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Conferences and Galas: Programs and Flyers, 1998-2014, undated; 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 12, 13)
  - Iban/Queer Koreans of New York: Sound Recording of Interview with Lee Chung-Woo (Chingusai-Seoul), 1998-12-06 (Box 8, Cassette 663.002, 663.007)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Creating Change Conference, 1998; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Pauline Park Name Badges, 1998-2014; 3 folders (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Political Activity and Training Sessions, 1998-2008; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Speaking Engagements 1998, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Iban/Queer Koreans of New York Reception for Chingusai-Seoul and Kiri-Kiri: May 8, 1999, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Speaking Engagements 1999, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Testimonies, 1999-2005; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Training Session and Workshop Materials, 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Children from the Shadows Conference, 2000; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Health and Human Services Network 2nd Annual Retreat, 2000; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Speaking Engagements 2000, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Transworld II Conference, 2000; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Empire State Pride Lobby Day 2001: Constituent Packet, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 18)